MBULELO PANI

ABOUT ME

I am a junior web developer, based in Cape Town. I have experience in building, testing and maintaining full stack websites. I also have experience working alone as well as working within a team, and I love to learn on the go. My passion is designing the functionality of neat and interactive websites.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Full name - Mbulelo Pani

Sex - Male

Date of Birth - 29/08/1997

Region - Cape Town, Western Cape

Nationality - South African

Email - Mbulelopani09@gmail.com

Phone - 073 703 6422

Web Profile - www.mbulelopani.herokuapp.com

EXPERIENCE

Oct 2021 - Feb, 2022 - Oviond

Web Developer Intern

- Integrations building & testing
- Frontend testing

Apr - July, 2021 - Touchfoundry

Web Developer Intern

- Frontend development
- Testing, debugging
- Code cleanup

EXPERIENCE

Nov - Apr, 2021 - LC Studio

Web Developer Intern

- Backend development
- Code testing and cleanup
- Frontend testing

Oct 2019 - Jan 2020 - Sage Futuremakers Foundation

Volunteer facilitator (part time)

- Assist facilitator in tutoring programming to youngsters
- Plan lessons
- Assist in recruiting potential students from the townships

EDUCATION

Feb- Aug, 2020 - Lifechoices Academy

Course: Fullstack Web Development

June - Nov, 2019 - Melisizwe Computer Lab Project

Course : Intro to Programming Certificate : Systems Development

2016 - Dec, 2018 - Northlink College

Course: Electrical Engineering

Certificate: N4

2011 - 2015 - Sizimisele Technical High School

Course: Electrical Engineering

Certificate: Matric

SKILLS

 $Frontend\ design$

HTML CSS Javascript Boostrap 4 Python

Mobile responsivenes ${\bf s}$

Frameworks

NodeJS React VueJS MongoDB Soft Skills

Teamwork
Accountability
Open-mindedness
Critical thinking
Time management

ACTIVITIES

Interests

Database design Machine learning Software design Robotics

Hobbies

Reading Meditation Circuit building Gaming

REFERENCES

Khanya Qongqo

NGO: Harare CAN Foundation **Position**: Marketer/manager

Contact: Qongqokhanya@gmail.com

Gift Khangamwa

NGO: Sage Future makers Foundation

Position: Facilitator

Contact: Gift@melisizwe.co.za